

CONTACT



07709 645 039



hi@robertgregg.co.uk



Flat 3, 9 Granville Road BN207EG



www.robertgregg.co.uk

PRO SKILLS



PERSONALITY

Motivated

Creative

Analytical

Team Work

Attitude

Problem Solving

ROBERT GREGG

Front End Web Designer/Software Engineer

I have a passion for coding and have enjoyed working on a wide range of projects. My past experience is mainly in front end development however I enjoy learning the new skills required in every project. I enjoy both being a part of a synergistic team and/or working alone.

I also have 15 years of experience in many other areas of business: marketing, communications, customer service, content creation, graphics design/video production/podcast production and more.

EXPERIENCE

OCT 2019 - OCT 2020

Junior Software Developer

MAR 2019 - SEPT 2020

Web Designer

JAN 2006 - AUG 2020

Director

MAY 2018 - FEB 2019

Web Designer

TRAINING

SWITCHPLANE

Agile/Scrum
 CSS3
 Javascript

Sourcetree
 PHP
 HTML

Building widgets/additional functionality on client sites / house projects, landing pages, website revamps, fixing bugs.

THE LITTLE DESIGN GROUP

WordpressHTMLCSS

Customizing client websites, often with awkward 3rd party apps, working to very tight deadlines under pressure.

SS4A/S3 STUDIOS

• Marketing Funnels • HTML/CSS Sites • Merchandise

Graphics/VideoWordpress

Business owner involved in all aspects for 15 years, including managing staff, virtual assistants and consultants

CLOUDY GROUP

Liaising with clients to create the desired website, from start to finish using Wordpress, HTML and CSS

HVAIMING

2019 - PRESENT

Home Learning

NOV 2020

Creative Process

2002 - 2005

University of West London

VARIOUS

Freecodecamp, Pluralsite, codeacademy, frontend Masters, Udemy (various), Azure fundamentals, YouTube (various), and more...

BCS LEVEL 4

Software Development Methodologies

BA HONS MULTIMEDIA COMPUTING

2.1

Learning various skills, html, Photoshop, Mysql, Javascript

REFERENCES

Joel Fielder Switchplane joel@switchplane.com Daniel Ceresia
The Little Design Group
dan@thelittlewineguy.com

David Hall
The Cloudy Group Ltd
david@cloudyit.co.uk